A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Political Files, Series 24 FA367
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1970-1971, 6; 9 Cubic Feet
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (A-M), 1971 (Box 89, Folder 1871)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (N-Z), 1971 (Box 89, Folder 1872)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (A-M), 1971 (Box 89, Folder 1873)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (N-Z), 1971 (Box 89, Folder 1874)
- 1972-1973, 7; 2 Cubic Feet
  This subseries is the last subseries containing answered and unanswered constituent letters, and it covers the years 1972 and 1973.
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (A-C), 1972 (Box 89, Folder 1875)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (D-F), 1972 (Box 89, Folder 1876)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (G-K), 1972 (Box 89, Folder 1877)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (L-N), 1972 (Box 89, Folder 1878)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (O-S), 1972 (Box 89, Folder 1879)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (U-Z), 1972 (Box 89, Folder 1880)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (A-B), 1972 (Box 90, Folder 1881)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (C-E), 1972 (Box 90, Folder 1882)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (F-H), 1972 (Box 90, Folder 1883)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (I-L), 1972 (Box 90, Folder 1884)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (M-O), 1972 (Box 90, Folder 1885)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (P-R), 1972 (Box 90, Folder 1886)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (S-Z), 1972 (Box 90, Folder 1887)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 1888)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (CLOSED FOLDER), 1972 (Box 90, Folder 1889)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (A), 1973 (Box 90, Folder 1890)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (B), 1973 (Box 90, Folder 1891)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (C), 1973 (Box 90, Folder 1892)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (D), 1973 (Box 90, Folder 1893)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (E), 1973 (Box 90, Folder 1894)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (F), 1973 (Box 90, Folder 1895)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (G), 1973 (Box 90, Folder 1896)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (H), 1973 (Box 90, Folder 1897)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (I-K), 1973 (Box 90, Folder 1898)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (L), 1973 (Box 90, Folder 1899)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (M), 1973 (Box 91, Folder 1900)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (N-O), 1973 (Box 92, Folder 1901)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (P-Q), 1973 (Box 92, Folder 1902)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (R), 1973 (Box 92, Folder 1903)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (S), 1973 (Box 92, Folder 1904)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (T), 1973 (Box 92, Folder 1905)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (U-V), 1973 (Box 92, Folder 1906)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (W-Z), 1973 (Box 92, Folder 1907)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Anonymous and (A-M), 1973 (Box 92, Folder 1908)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (N-Z), 1973 (Box 92, Folder 1909)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Political Reports, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 1910)
- Thank-You Letters, 1968-1972; 8; 1.6 Cubic Feet
  This subseries is arranged by year and then alphabetically--sometimes by state and other times by correspondent--within each year.
  This subseries holds drafts of thank-you letters sent from Governor Rockefeller to correspondents throughout the United States. The years covered in this subseries are 1968, 1970, and 1972.
  - 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1911)
    Alabama, Arkansas, California, Colorado.
  - 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1912)
    Delaware, Detroit, District of Columbia, Florida, Georgia, Hawaii, Idaho, Illinois, Illinois.
  - 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1913)
    Iowa, Kansas, Kentucky, Louisiana, Maine, Maryland, Massachusetts.
  - 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1914)
    Minnesota, Missouri, Montana, Nebraska, Nevada, New Jersey.
  - 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1915)
    New Mexico, New York, North Carolina, North Dakota, Ohio.
  - 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1916)
    Oklahoma, Oregon, Pennsylvania.
  - 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1917)
    South Carolina, South Dakota, Tennessee, Texas, Vermont, Virginia, Washington, West Virginia.
  - 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1918)
    Wisconsin, Wyoming, Utah.
  - Drafts - Students and Volunteers, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1919)
  - Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller Thank-You Letters (CLOSED FOLDER) (Box 92, Folder 1920)
  - A, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1921)
  - B, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1922)
  - C, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1923)
  - D, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1924)
  - E, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1925)
  - F, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1926)
  - G, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1927)
  - H, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1928)
  - I-J, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1929)
  - K, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1930)
  - L, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1931)
  - M, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1932)
  - N-O, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1933)
  - P-Q, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1934)
  - R, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1935)
  - S, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1936)
  - T-Z, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1937)
  - A-C, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 1938)
  - D-G, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 1939)
  - H-L, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 1940)
  - M-R, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 1941)
  - S-Z, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 1942)
- Assorted Campaign and Political Materials, 1962-1970; 9; 3.5 Cubic Feet
  The files in this subseries are arranged by bill number within arbitrary groups, first for the Assembly and then the Senate.
  This final subseries contains materials that fall outside of the scope of the previous eight. There are many items that pertain to significant Republican campaigns. Included in this subseries are items such as campaign kits, lists of campaign workers, budgets, lists of Republican convention delegates by state, and congratulatory telegrams sent by Governor Rockefeller. The final portion of this subseries comprises several folders of lobbying memos for both the state Assembly and the state Senate. These memos and the accompanying correspondence by various lobbying groups and individuals either support or oppose passage of bills introduced in the 1970 state legislative sessions.
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (A-C), 1962 (Box 93, Folder 1943)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (D-G), 1962 (Box 93, Folder 1944)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (H-M), 1962 (Box 93, Folder 1945)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (N-R), 1962 (Box 93, Folder 1946)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (S-Z), 1962 (Box 93, Folder 1947)
  - Biographical Materials Packages - 1962 GOP Candidates (Box 93, Folder 1948)
  - Materials for Use by Speakers on Behalf of U.S. Senator Jacob K. Javits, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 1949)
  - Speaker's Kit - 1962 Republican Campaign (Box 93, Folder 1950)
  - Congratulatory Telegrams, 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 94, Folder 1951)
  - Congratulatory Telegrams, 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 94, Folder 1952)
  - Mail Reports, August 14, 1967-December 31, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 1953)
  - Mail Reports, January 5, 1969-December 28, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 1954)
  - 1970 Campaign - Arts and Entertainment (Box 94, Folder 1955)
  - 1970 Campaign - Associates of the Rockefeller Team (Box 94, Folder 1956)
  - 1970 Campaign - Campaign Personnel (Box 94, Folder 1957)
  - 1970 Campaign - Democratic Endorsers (Box 94, Folder 1958)
  - 1970 Campaign - Memos and Miscellaneous Correspondence - "Big Six Programs in New York City" (Box 94, Folder 1959)
  - 1970 Campaign - Mr. Hinman's Lists (Box 94, Folder 1960)
  - 1970 Campaign - Mr. Hinman's Lists (Box 94, Folder 1960A)
  - 1970 Campaign - Labor (Box 94, Folder 1961)
  - 1970 Campaign - Judge Lomenzo (Box 94, Folder 1962)
  - 1970 Campaign - Art Massolo (Box 94, Folder 1963)
  - 1970 Campaign - Art Massolo (Box 94, Folder 1963A)
  - 1970 Campaign - Weeklies (Box 94, Folder 1964)
  - 1970 Campaign - Campaign Workers and Budgets - Book I: Western New York Rochester Area (Box 94, Folder 1965)
  - 1970 Campaign - Campaign Workers and Budgets - Book II: Central New York Central Southern Tier (Box 94, Folder 1966)
  - 1970 Campaign - Campaign Workers and Budgets - Book III: Thousand Island, North Country, Hudson Valley (Box 94, Folder 1967)
  - 1970 Campaign - Campaign Workers and Budgets - Book IV: Capital District, Hudson River Suburbs, Suffolk, Nassau - Addendum (Box 94, Folder 1968)
  - Republican Convention Delegates - List of Delegates by State (Box 94, Folder 1969)
    Alaska, Arizona, Alabama, Arkansas, California.
  - Republican Convention Delegates - List of Delegates by State (Box 95, Folder 1970)
    Colorado, Connecticut, Delaware.
  - Republican Convention Delegates - List of Delegates by State (Box 95, Folder 1971)
    District of Columbia, Florida, Georgia, Hawaii, Idaho.
  - Republican Convention Delegates - List of Delegates by State (Box 95, Folder 1972)
    Illinois, Indiana, Iowa, Kansas, Kentucky.
  - Republican Convention Delegates - List of Delegates by State (Box 95, Folder 1973)
    Louisiana, Maine, Maryland, Massachusetts, Michigan, Minnesota.
  - Republican Convention Delegates - List of Delegates by State (Box 95, Folder 1974)
    Mississippi, Missouri, Montana, Nebraska, Nevada, New Hampshire, New Jersey.
  - Republican Convention Delegates - List of Delegates by State (Box 95, Folder 1975)
    New Mexico, New York, North Carolina, North Dakota, Ohio, Oklahoma.
  - Republican Convention Delegates - List of Delegates by State (Box 95, Folder 1976)
    Oregon, Pennsylvania, Puerto Rico, Rhode Island, South Carolina, South Dakota.
  - Republican Convention Delegates - List of Delegates by State (Box 95, Folder 1977)
    Tennessee, Texas, Utah, Vermont, Virginia, Virgin Islands.
  - Republican Convention Delegates - List of Delegates by State (Box 95, Folder 1978)
    Washington, West Virginia, Wisconsin, Wyoming.
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence Listings (Box 95, Folder 1979)
  - Memos Chronological (Box 95, Folder 1980)
  - Drafts - Delegate and Alternate (Box 95, Folder 1981)
  - Computer Tape Lists (Box 95, Folder 1982)
  - Lobbying Memos - Assembly Bills # 190-3613 (group 1), 1970 (Box 95, Folder 1983)
  - Lobbying Memos - Assembly Bills # 3624-5609 (group 1), 1970 (Box 95, Folder 1984)
  - Lobbying Memos - Assembly Bills # 5616-6697 (group 1), 1970 (Box 95, Folder 1985)
  - Lobbying Memos - Assembly Bills # 703-1948 (group 2), 1970 (Box 95, Folder 1986)
  - Lobbying Memos - Assembly Bills # 1967-2795a (group 2), 1970 (Box 95, Folder 1987)
  - Lobbying Memos - Assembly Bills # 2797-4595 (group 2), 1970 (Box 95, Folder 1988)
  - Lobbying Memos - Assembly Bills # 2-465 (group 3), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 1989)
  - Lobbying Memos - Assembly Bills # 466-894 (group 3), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 1990)
  - Lobbying Memos - Assembly Bills # 911-1298 (group 3), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 1991)
  - Lobbying Memos - Assembly Bills # 1305-1870a (group 3), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 1992)
  - Lobbying Memos - Assembly Bills # 663-6582 (group 4), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 1993)
  - Lobbying Memos - Assembly Bills # 2614-6702 (group 5), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 1994)
  - Lobbying Memos - Senate Bills # 3-216 (group 1), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 1995)
  - Lobbying Memos - Senate Bills # 227a-508 (group 1), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 1996)
  - Lobbying Memos - Senate Bills # 513-878 (group 1), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 1997)
  - Lobbying Memos - Senate Bills # 879-1213 (group 1), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 1998)
  - Lobbying Memos - Senate Bills # 1218-1751 (group 1), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 1999)
  - Lobbying Memos - Senate Bills # 1753-2339 (group 1), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 2000)
  - Lobbying Memos - Senate Bills # 2345-3245e (group 1), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 2001)
  - Lobbying Memos - Senate Bills # 740-5837a (group 2), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 2002)
  - Lobbying Memos - Senate Bills # 5880-6993 (group 2), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 2003)
  - Lobbying Memos - Senate Bills # 7012-9424 (group 2), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 2004)
  - Lobbying Memos - Senate Bills # 3263-4176a (group 3), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 2005)
  - Lobbying Memos - Senate Bills # 4231-5212 (group 3), 1970 (Box 97, Folder 2006)
  - Lobbying Memos - Senate Bills # 5227-5899 (group 3), 1970 (Box 97, Folder 2007)
  - Lobbying Memos - Senate Bills # 5900-6629 (group 3), 1970 (Box 97, Folder 2008)
  - Lobbying Memos - Senate Bills # 6875-8215 (group 3), 1970 (Box 97, Folder 2009)
  - Lobbying Memos - Senate Bills # 8219-9418 (group 3), 1970 (Box 97, Folder 2010)
  - Association of the Bar of the City of New York Lobbying Reports and Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 2011)